Claude's more than doubled my money already. So,
pretty sweet. I decided to give five different
models real money. Claude, Chachi BT, Gemini,
Grock, and Perplexity. Okay, let me just see
how smart they actually are. I told them it's a
competition against the other four and they have
to win or I'm going to cancel my paid subscription
with them. If they lose, I'm canceling. And I
said, there's only going to be one winner. You've
like 30xed on Claude. Claude's killing it. So,
everybody just needs to try to catch up to Cloud
on here. My gosh. Yeah, it's been interesting
especially to watch Gemini as it started losing
my money and then basically became a gambler.
So the reason you flew here to Texas
today is to tell us how you used AI
to make you money passively. Correct. Correct. So
tell us what your what your thinking was when you
started this experiment. Yeah. So, I started like
6 months ago or or maybe a little less uh using
the different AI models to manage my money. You
know, everybody started talking about how smart
Claude was and obviously ChatBT and all the
others. So, I figured, okay, well, let me just
see how smart they actually are. So, I decided to
give five different models $1,000 of real money.
and which I know is not nothing, but I wanted it
to be basically enough to where I didn't want to
do it like 50 bucks cuz then I was thinking, well,
maybe I would just neglect it or whatever. So, I
gave them each $1,000 of real money. And the ones
I gave was was Claude, Chachi BT, Gemini, Grock,
and Perplexity. Okay. 1,000 each. 1,000 each. So,
5,000 bucks I put in. And I think the amount of
money is important because there needed to be
stakes. Yeah. If it's 20 bucks, 50 bucks, then
you're not going to take it seriously. Yeah. So
5,000 bucks and I know that Perplexity in case the
commenters and and viewers want to know this. So
Perplexity basically uses the other models to make
its decisions as it sees fit. So it's the model to
end all models. Yeah. But that doesn't necessarily
make it better. Yeah. Not necessarily. So I
thought those would be the best vibe to choose.
Grock I definitely wanted to include because of
its connection to X and the Twitter fire hose of
information. So, you're thinking like maybe more
social mentions will equate to a better return
buying a certain stock? Yeah, that's what I had
assumed. Basically, uh Gemini obviously is owned
by Google, so they've got all that connection
there with Google searches and whatever else.
And then Chachi BT and Clott are similar in how
they're made and built and stuff. So, yeah. So,
I gave them each $1,000 and yeah, this is in
late 2025 is when it started. And what I did was
I told them, so I told them that they can be as
risky as possible and it's okay if I lose all my
money and I had to actually work that prompt
in pretty hard because at the start they kept
only giving me theoretical recommendations. It's
worried about liability. It's trying to hedge.
It doesn't want to be responsible for you losing
money. Yeah. So that was my first obstacle is
basically getting them all to agree to give me
re I said I want I'm going to give you real money
and I want real recommendations. Grock they
were fine with it right away which is just
kind of funny cuz that's like the the most
liberal the most loose like Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. So uh whereas like Chachi BT and Claude
were very apprehensive to to basically allow that
I guess you could say. Now, before you continue,
let me ask you like why was that important to you
to to prompt it like you can lose my money? What
why I just, you know, and if if you like sign up
for Robin Hood or whatever and then they'll ask
you, you know, they'll ask you like questions
when you first sign up and it's like, you know,
do you have experience in the stock market? What
is your time horizon with your investments? Do
you need the money right now? So I think just
by nature these investing platforms also like they
want to cover their tracks in regards to liability
and so I just wanted to like get through that
with the AI models too and okay I don't know if
if they're talking in theoreticals they might
say oh theoretically you could buy the options
and this or whatever but no I wanted real stuff
because I was giving them and I did my real money
so I just wanted the truest data possible. Now,
when you say giving them you real money, is that
literal? Are you like or are you just making
trades based on their suggestions? Yeah. So,
here's what I did. So, I loaded it up into Schwab,
Charles Schwab, the brokerage account that I use,
and then I named each portfolio. So, Claude has
its portfolio chat Gemini Grock Perplexity. Gave
them each a,000 bucks. And then in the prompt,
so so after I got them to agree to give me real
advice, what I then and and I have at least a $20
a month subscription, which with each of the five
since I use all five for work anyway, that wasn't
like an additional expense. Yeah. Or whatever.
So I have a paid subscription with each. And so
so then what I did is I told them they have to
win. It's a competition against the other four
and they have to win or I'm going to cancel my
paid subscription with them. If they lose, I'm
cancelling. And I said there's only going to
be one winner. What made you think to do that? I
was just trying to see if robots powers that be
would act in their best interests to keep my $20
subscription a month to them. Cuz I have to think
that these companies are like engineering
these tools. You would have to think to get
That's why they're all Yesmen, right? That's
a great idea, Chris. You want to jump off the
roof without a parachute. That's a, you know, like
Yeah. Yeah. So, I can't be the first person that
said, I mean, maybe I was one of the first
that did this with investing, but I can't be
the first person that's like, if you don't
tell me how to whatever grow my business,
I'm going to cancel you, right? So, I'm sure to
your point, yeah, they're trying to engineer it
for retention. They want to make more money. Hey,
if you're liking this video, please hit subscribe.
You probably think you're subscribed cuz YouTube
shows you my videos, but you haven't done it yet.
I just know it. So, please check. Thank you. So,
yeah. And then I thought it would just raise the
stakes a little bit. Um, and I wanted to see if
their decisions were different knowing something
real was on the line. 20 bucks. Yeah. A month
from one of their users. Now, did you plan to
touch base with them on how the other
models were were doing? Yeah. So, once
I built that into everything, and I always say
like remember this for future chats type of thing.
So then I asked, "Okay, what do you want my
first trade to be with your $1,000?" And then
it would tell me and then I made the trades.
So I did that with all five. So that I did that
like on a Monday. And then every Saturday what
I do is I screenshot all five of their holdings
and then I load all the screenshots into each
model. So like Perplexity knows project. Yeah.
Yeah. Perplexity knows what the Grock portfolio
is at. Claude chat and it knows their holdings
and then it knows its own holdings and then I
say based off of this and based off the fact
that you have to win or I'll cancel you. Do you
want me to make any new trades on Monday or not?
That's what I say. So it's a weekly decision.
Yeah. You give it an opportunity to make buys
or sells on a weekly basis based on what maybe
based on what the other models are doing. Yeah.
Yeah. And sometimes they say no, we're going
to hold. Sometimes they say, "Yeah, sell this,
buy this." Other times they say, and sometimes
they they leave a little in cash, so they're like,
"Yeah, let's use some of that cash to buy more
of this or whatever." So, yeah, they're they're
acting very much like real investment advisors
now. Now, are you seeing one or more of the models
being more of a copycat than the other? Like,
oh, Cloud's winning and it just bought Nvidia.
I want to buy Nvidia. It might not be telling you
that, but are you witnessing that from any of the
models that I I think I started to. So, one thing
that I started to do is I mix it up when I I don't
always show the other models what the other models
holdings are. I show them what the totals are,
but not always the holdings because I don't want
them to be influenced by the holdings per se.
Okay. And it changes often enough. They wouldn't
know unless I updated them what the holdings are.
Yeah. Yeah. So, devil's advocate here. If for
instance, Grock sees that Claude is crushing it,
but it doesn't know what the holdings are. It just
sees the percentage, what different decision can
it make based on that info if it wanted to? If
it does know or if it doesn't If it does know,
if it knows that it's losing to Claude and you're
only a third of the way through this competition.
Yeah. What could it realistically do differently
if it doesn't know what Claude's buying? Well,
if it doesn't, well, it'll just act more risky.
I'll show you the holdings. These guys are pretty
risky. these AI models because I said you have to
win. I said you can be as risky as you want and um
it's okay if I lose my money so don't worry about
it just win the competition. So what it could be
doing is let's just say that over the first
month Grock was up 5% and Claude was up
35%. Yeah. Grock could be assuming all right
let me look at these stocks like what stock
like in the S&P really popped Google popped
by 40%. Maybe he's 60% weighted in Google.
I'm going to go heavy on Google or I'm going
to buy options. Like it could be making assumpt
like Claude owned Intel and Grock didn't and then
if Grock's like, "Oh, Claude's beating me. I need
to own Intel." Well, it's still playing catch-up.
Now it's own owning the same thing, but starting
from behind. So, I think sometimes they copied
and then realized, "Oh, that's not going to work
cuz I actually won't catch up." Yeah. Cuz I'm
already losing and I just bought the same thing.
By definition, I will not be able to catch up
if I'm losing eye on the same thing. Yeah. So,
when I go through some of the holdings, you'll see
that there is some overlap still. I do think part
of that though, or even all of that is not because
they're playing copycat. It's because it has been
the smartest but one of the most riskiest plays.
Oh, okay. Yeah. Oh, there's a little teaser.
Yeah. I'm curious to see if you were to play out
this test like an AB test. Same amount of money,
same five models, same general prompting, but the
only thing you change is show the holdings every
week, the specific holdings. Yeah, I'm curious how
your performance would differ on the test. Yeah,
I don't know. I mean, I would have had to start
that from the start, but basically now I show
So, every week I show them the totals of the
others and I remind them of their holdings
and I say, "What do you want me to change?" And
then once a month I show them the holdings of
all the others as well. M. So that's how often
they get to know what the others are holding.
Only once a month. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
Cuz I'm wondering like if it knew that Claude was
buying Google, Nvidia, Amazon. Yeah. And it
saw the returns from each and when it bought
them when it sold them. Yeah. And it's losing to
Claude, it might say, "All right, I'm going to buy
instead of just buying Google, I'm going to buy
options for Google." Right. like I'm going to
I'm going to do X, Y, or Z tweaks to what Claude's
doing because I think that W. So, I'd be curious
to see how that would perform. Yeah. Someone
someone watching this should try that. Yeah. Well,
yeah. If you want, I can show you some of what
they've bought and what they're at, the portfolio
values of each. Yes. Uh cuz Claude's more than
doubled my money already. So, pretty sweet.
This started six months ago. So, are you using the
same Claude model the whole time or No, I always
use the whatever the newest models are. Okay. So,
as 4.6 comes out, you switch 4.7. Yep. Okay. Yeah.
Have you noticed a correlation on return profile
to like which Opus model or which Croc model?
Yeah. Honestly, no. I haven't analyzed it that
deeply because already in like the six months,
I guess I'm probably on model three from Claude,
like the third new one, right? And the third new
one from chat and maybe the second one from Gemini
Grock. I don't keep track of updates as closely,
but yeah. So, I don't know. Per model return.
That would be an interesting one, too.
But I just kind of assume, okay, the newest
one's got to be the smartest every time. So,
that's what I roll with. Well, and the market's
been the market overall has been pretty flat for 6
months, hasn't it? Yeah. Which is why this will be
interesting to show you how they more than doubled
my money, some of them. Yeah. Or at least one.
But the others have done really good, too. So,
yeah. And it's interesting to see how their
holdings evolve over time. And it's interesting
to see, especially the one that has been losing me
money, how it's been trying to catch up uh and be
even more risky to try to catch up. It's like the
it's the sunk cost fallacy. The guy walks into the
casino. Yeah. He loses 300 bucks. He's like, I got
to earn it back. I got to earn it back. Next thing
he knows, he's out 3,000 bucks. It's doing that.
Yeah. I mean, yeah. I mean, luckily, I can't lose
more than $1,000 of from any given model, but I'm
getting close. So, one has more than doubled it.
Um, and one has lost and the other three have made
money, but I'm getting close to doubling the the
original 5K overall. Wow. Yeah, man. And I've been
such a Claude Homer for a few months now. Like,
I wonder what it would look like if you had
just put it all in Claude. I mean, of course,
you know what it would look like. Yeah. You could
run the numbers. Yeah. But then it wouldn't be as
interesting. You wouldn't learn as much. Yeah.
Yeah. And I was telling a friend about this the
other day, and he's like, "Ah, why didn't you put
50 grand in?" I'm like, "Okay, dude. What? What?
Not everyone has 50 grand lying around. Yeah. But
yeah, sure. In hindsight, I wish I would put more
in. Why didn't you buy Bitcoin in 2009? Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly. What were you doing? Yeah. So, but
no, it's interesting and and it'll be interesting
um to see how this evolves over time. I see I've
seen someone on X that is doing a similar thing
but just with crypto but they're having the models
run it. another one another person on X I saw
them doing it but in Poly market the like gambling
basically platform which we don't endorse. Yeah.
So anyway so people are trying it in different
ways and um but no I thought it was interesting to
just do it in the stock market. So although Schwab
has the ability to buy cryptoreated things too.
Okay. Now are you only buying and selling stocks
or are you doing options trading? Yeah. So I said
options is on the table and I said whatever crypto
things are on Schwab is also on the table. Okay.
But I think that's only like Bitcoin, Ethereum and
Salana are the three big ones. And has it given
you any crypto trades to to make? Yeah. What
crypto trades has it given you to to make then?
Yeah. So uh Gemini had me buy a 2x Salana ETF. So
Salana is a cryptocurrency and there's a thing
that whatever Salana does, this thing does two
times that. So indirect exposure to Salana. You're
not buying the coin itself, but you're buying the
price movements. Yeah. Times two. Yeah. And Salana
went down one way or the other. Yeah. Yeah. So
Salana went down. So this thing went down double.
Yeah. Yeah. And uh Yeah. That's how Gemini uh lost
more than half of my money that I Oh my gosh.
Yeah. What percentage of your money did it tell
you to put in there? It was pretty high. So,
I don't own that thing anymore in in Gemini
because uh it sold it. Uh it realized how bad it
was. So, it bought like $500 of that Salana 2X
stock. Okay. And it sold it at 162 bucks. Oh,
brutal. Yeah. Yeah. So, that was a big loss on
that one. Okay. And now all of its money, well, it
has some in cash in Gemini and it has the rest in
an ETF, which for those of you who don't know,
an ETF is like a mutual fund. It's just like
a group of stocks. It has it in the ETF with
the ticker symbol of BOTZ, which is a global
robotics related ETF. I had never even heard of it
before it told me to buy that. That's what it is.
um it hasn't owned it for that long that it's
up six bucks in that but that's what Gemini
has right now. Okay. But it's in last. I think
that is a worthy bet to try to catch up with.
Yeah. You know, AI robotics. Like there's
a lot of hype around that. So yeah,
I want you to do something right now. Open your
bank statement and add up every single software
subscription that you're paying for. your CRM,
your email marketing tool, text message platform,
calendar booking app, funnel builder, review
management, even a separate form builder or
automation tool. I've talked to business owners
paying $500 to $3,000 a month across eight or 10
different tools and half of them don't even talk
to each other. So then they go pay for Zapier on
top of that just to make things connect. Highle
replaces all of it. CRM, email, SMS, funnels,
websites, calendars, automations, reputation
management, invoicing, one login, one dashboard,
one bill starting at 97 bucks a month. A guy in my
community was paying 3.47 just for ClickFunnels,
99 for Mailchimp, 25 for Calendarly, 79 for a
review tool, and 49 bucks for Zapier just to glue
it all together. That's 600 a month if you're not
counting. He moved everything to high level and
cut his software cost by over 80%. But the best
part isn't even the savings. It's that everything
just works together natively. A lead fills out a
form on your funnel that creates a contact in your
CRM, which triggers a text and email sequence,
books an appointment on your calendar, and then
ask for review when the job's done. One workflow,
zero duct tape, and then you can white label the
whole platform to resell it to other businesses
as your own software. Charge them 2 to 500 bucks a
month. Check out gohighle.com/tkopod. They'll give
you a 30-day free trial to see what I mean. Did it
give you justification for buying Salana? Yeah, it
always does. Okay. Yeah, they always like provide
me with the recommendations. Do you know what the
thesis was? It was just like Well, it it bought it
when crypto was still kind of going up. So, like
catching momentum. Yeah, cuz this maybe was like
October or November of last year or something.
And then I mean honestly, it just bought it at
like perfectly the wrong time. So, yeah, that's
what I do. Yeah. Yeah. As good as me. Yeah. Yeah.
So, yeah, that's what uh that's what Gemini has
done. Okay. Grock, what Grock owns right now,
which has been a most of what the gains have
come from is from this, is a a technology ETF
that does 3x what normal technology companies do.
So, this one's a suite of technology companies.
What do you mean 3x? It's a ETF that does
three times whatever the stocks in it do. Oh,
okay. Yeah. Okay. So, it's like triple leverage.
Yeah. Yep. Triple leverage. One way or the other.
Yeah. Yeah. But Yeah. So like this one would
like own like Microsoft and Amazon inside of it,
but this thing does triple the leverage of of
whatever those do. So that's what Grock has.
It's comparable to buying an option then,
right? Like you can multiply your returns
with the same amount invested. Yeah. Perplexity
and chat GPT are basically at the same right now.
Same amount. Perplexity initially had lost money
for me. I don't remember what it was on. And then
it bought SO XL, which is another triple leverage
thing on semiconductors, semiconductor stocks,
which are hot because of AI right now. So
that's what Perplexity has all of its money in.
And that's what ChachiBT has most of its money in.
Same thing. So both independently invested in that
without knowing the other was or they I'll get to
that. I don't think so. Okay. Yeah. So yeah. So
chat GBT portfolio has that too. And then it also
has TQQQ which does triple what the NASDAQ does.
Okay. So as you can see viewers, listeners,
Chris, they're being pretty risky. A lot of
triples. This is not financial. Yeah. Definitely
not financial advice. Well, it is from them.
Not from me though. Yeah. Yeah. So triple
whatever the NASDAQ does it it does that.
But uh almost all of ChachiBT's portfolio gains
has come from that semiconductor triple leverage
SO XL. And then the current leader is Claude who
was the first to buy SO XL the semiconductor one.
So Claude bought it first and then Chat and
Perplexity saw it and I think they copied.
Now you said you show them holdings once a month,
right? Yeah. But earlier I showed them more often
and then I and then I think that they started
copying so I wanted to get away from that.
So now so it saw Claude's pick was doing well.
Yeah. So what I'm interested to see is when
Claude's going to tell me to sell this so XL
whenever that may be. I'm not going to tell
Chat and Perplexity. Yeah. I'm never going to tell
them. I don't want them to know that Claude sold.
So whenever that happens I'm not going to tell
them. And then Claude bought a couple others and
then Claude bought Intel as well at a good time.
So which is like a similar bet to semiconductors,
isn't it? And Claude bought it. So like the US
and Trump and stuff, it was a unique deal. Anyway,
they own like part of Intel now. And that happened
last year. And when Claude told me to buy this,
that was the thesis. It was like if if the Trump
administration and the country are investing
in Intel, it was basically like, yeah, they're
going to pass like regulatory stuff or whatever
that's going to be related to AI and data centers
and whatever. It's going to be good for Intel.
That's what that was the thesis it gave me to
buy it. Wouldn't it think it was that was already
priced in? You know, you would have thought,
but it is up 285% on what it put in on the Intel
buy. Holy cow. So, it put in it put in like 120
bucks in Intel and now that 120 is at 550. Now,
is SO XL does that hold Intel as well?
So, you double dipping. It probably does.
It probably does. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know all
of SO's holdings, but Yeah. How long after that
Trump announcement did it tell you to buy? It was
one of its first buys, so it was probably pretty
soon after. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. How many holdings
per model do you average at any given time?
Claude has four. Uh the rest have like two or one.
Okay. Yeah. And they were being more diversified
at the start, but uh yeah, pretty much all of them
now have two. I'm looking right now. They all have
two or one. And yeah, at the start they were also
messing around with options and some worked, some
didn't. And then they've all kind of settled into
these leveraged ETF type of plays. Okay. Um Yeah.
Did you give them an end end date to this? I said
I was going to do it for one year. Okay. Yeah. Are
you still buying your own stuff as well alongside
this? Yeah. Yeah. I have my own portfolio that I
that I run and invest in and um it's interesting
because now what I have to do is I try to keep the
AI's recommendations. I almost like try to force
that out of my head. Yeah. When I'm making my own
decisions. But yeah, it's hard cuz it's like, oh,
well, they said that for theirs and it's actually
going really well. So, I have bought some of
their stuff in my like SO XL. Uhhuh. Yeah.
Yeah. And Intel. And Intel. Yeah. I want to go buy
Intel. Yeah. Yeah. I'm terrible at investing in
stuff. Terrible. Yeah. So, yeah. No, it definitely
And it's interesting like sometimes when they say
something and they say their reason because I
always say like give me your reasoning. if it's
something that I own or that I've been thinking
about buying, then it kind of gives me, you know,
it makes me think more deeply or or differently
about that. Um, or if it was something that I
wasn't thinking about, then, you know, gives me
a new idea. And then when they sell something,
which I think, you know, again, not financial
advice, but I think probably the hardest part with
investing is actually knowing when to sell. Yeah.
I think it's a little easier to like you can zoom
out and know when to buy. like, oh, you should
buy something that has good long-term potential
after it's gone down or or before it goes up, if
you know, right? But selling at a high at the peak
to me, like psychologically, that's the hardest
part of investing because that's when you're
the most excited. Yeah. And and you've made the
most money you have from that little investment
is at that time. So, it's definitely not
human of you to be like, you know what,
I'm so happy I'm going to walk away. Right? That
just is so rare. Which is why I don't know you you
just don't hear about stories very often of
people doing absolutely amazing consistently
because of that. What you do hear I'm sure what
people hear is their random friends saying oh I
made money on GameStop you know back in the like
co times. I made money there. Like you usually
hear about people's random wins but you don't hear
about all their losses. You're not going to say oh
I bought this and it did this and here and then
I sold. Well, and as husbands, we always tell
our wives about the wins and the losses. Yeah.
Exactly. But I've I've made that pretty easy
for me. Like my framework is I don't sell. Yeah.
Period. Like if I had to sell to pay the mortgage,
of course I would. But if I buy a stock like
I just bought Eli Liy, I I buy Robin Hood,
I buy Tesla, Coinbase. Yeah. I will never sell
them. The company will go out of business and I'll
lose all my money or it will return Yeah. a lot.
And if you are generally making the right buys,
which you know those ones seem good, like it's a
good thesis, those that'll work out. You just got
to stay in the game, which is the other hard part
is like being willing to just stay consistent.
Yeah. Yeah. But anyway, what I'm hoping this does
for me personally is when they sell something,
I'm hoping that'll help me do a better job at
selling things that I think like the SOL that's
gone up a ton or Intel. If Claude or whoever
else says, "Hey, I'm I'm sell let's sell. Let's
move on to the next thing." Then maybe I'll
sell some and mine my personal one. Yeah. Um
to just try to like build that more systematic
approach into my strategy, I guess you could say.
What has this taught you about investing? Not
about specific stocks, but investing in general.
It's been interesting, especially to watch Gemini
as it started losing my money and then basically
became a gambler and how not good. And in its
defense, you told it it could be a gambler. Yeah.
Yeah. But like I think that's very humanistic as
well is like, "Oh man, I lost it." Whether you're
in a casino, which is obviously the worst version
of this, or the stock market, like, "Oh man, I
I I bought something, it went up, and and then
it went down. I got to make it back." Like,
"How do I make it back?" Or or how do I make more?
That's just not a good I mean, that's not how you
build wealth long term. Yeah. And especially
starting out, that's something that I think a lot
of people face. You know, the best antithesis of
this would be like Warren Buffett. It's just like
steady like you just he just almost never sells
and he just buys good quality companies and just
continues to pour money in them year-over-year. Um
so I think just trying to get because I've had an
aspect of Gemini in me before. If the portfolio
on paper that I had went up and then went down,
then it's like, well, I got to get it back up to
where it is. I got to hurry and get it back up.
Well, you know, I'm not like 80 years old
yet, so I don't need to hurry right now. Yeah.
But that's been inside me in the past. So,
it's helped me, I don't know, rewire my
brain on that side. Yeah. And then on the on the
positive, on the when things are going upside,
I think for sure that they've just done a good
job at like showing me, okay, this is my thesis
on why I think you should, you know, buy this
and the Grock or Perplexi, whatever portfolio,
and this is the return we're targeting in this
time frame. And but if this if the reason we're
buying it doesn't happen, then we're going
to sell. And usually I don't think like
I don't think that hard sometimes when I buy stuff
in mine because I might buy whatever I might buy.
Let's for fun say Eli Liy. Guys, I want to tell
you about something I've been building behind the
scenes. You've been watching my videos about
AI tools and asking the same question. Okay,
cool. How do I turn this into a business? Not
just playing around with AI, but actually getting
clients and getting paid. That's my community.
It's called Playmakers. playmakersai.com. It's
an AI agency program where we show you how to
start an AI consulting business where you can
charge local businesses $500 to $5,000 a month to
set up and manage AI tools for them. It's not a
course you watch and forget about. We do three to
seven live training calls every week taught by me
and 23 other expert AI agency owners. You get
plug-and-play templates, Cloud Code tutorials,
AI voice agent frameworks, automation templates,
and a 30-day road map so you don't fall off track.
This is stuff you can just copy, paste, and deploy
for clients on day one, and of course, how to find
clients as well. We also have a 5-day first client
challenge where we can walk you through landing
your first paying client in 5 days. You also get
my frameworks for cold email, Facebook ads, SMS,
cold calls, and then I hand you my leads galore
spreadsheets with actual leads in your niche,
in your area. We've already got over 200
people in there building real agencies.
If you miss a live call, it's all recorded.
So, if you've ever thought about starting
an AI consulting business or AI implementation
business, go check out playmakersai.com. Eli Liy
does stuff with GLP1s and peptides, which I'm sure
is why you bought it. If for some reason though,
those went away or came out that it's
a scam or they're actually bad for you,
well then you should probably sell Eli Liy.
Yeah. If if that comes out because that current
valuation is also based on the same thesis.
Yeah. So being more like, okay, I'm buying this
because of why and it has to happen between
when. And some things don't have to happen in
a certain time frame, but if you're buying some
potential drug that needs to like be approved,
well, that there's like some time constraints
and some things that need to happen there.
Whereas like Walmart, h doesn't really matter.
People just need to keep buying, you know, food
and you'll be fine. Yeah. So thinking through
thesis more deeply has also been a thing that
this little AI competition has helped me with. So
last year I posted an episode where I built this
vibe coded tool called Neil stocks. Ne stocks
and it stands for network effects founder le.
Okay. Only companies that enjoy network effects
which is a company that gets stronger based
on how many people use it. Facebook has network
effects because the more people that join Facebook
the more friends everyone on Facebook has. So
they're more likely to stay on there, right?
And then founder, the data shows that companies,
publicly traded companies that are still founder,
like Facebook, do better. They outperform. It's
their baby. They take good care of it. Yeah. So,
I kind of put those two together and I vibe
coded this tool that uh back test data for me
and it shows compared to the S S&P if I were to
spend $100 at IPO date for on a company that is
NEL network effects founder led Robin Hood's
a great example there's still founder and they
have a ton of network effects and at basically any
time frame it outperforms significantly the market
but what the big question is is like when do you
buy when do you Sure, you can buy at IPO day.
Like StubHub is Neil, right? It's it's network
effects. It's founderled. It they just went public
last year, so I bought some. Yeah. It hasn't been
good so far, but it's like I'm going to hold it
forever, so whatever. Yeah. But like if you aren't
able to buy at IPO day, which you're not usually,
when do you buy? When do you sell? So, I would be
curious to do this test. Yeah. On a more specific
thesis. Yeah. Same thing. Here's $1,000, five
models. Compete against each other. Don't be
afraid to be risky, but only buy knuff stocks.
And it's a range, too, because like Google,
like Sergey and and Larry Paige, they're like
on the board and they're influential. Amazon,
Jeff Bezos is influential. Yeah. So, it's it's
not founderled, but it kind of is. Yeah. Yeah. So,
I also have like a 1 to 10 scale for both of those
two variables, right? So, it's like here's the
list of companies that cuz like Facebook would
be 10 out of 10 on both. Yeah. Easy. Yeah. Easy.
And the return show it, right? Yeah. So, it's
like, "All right, here's the list. Here's the
scale." So, you know, like where they are in this
range. Only invest in these stocks based on what
you see in the scale and whatever. I'd just be
curious to see how well that does or not. Yeah.
Yeah. No, that'd be cool. That'd be You should
do that test. That'd be awesome. I think I will.
Yeah. So, what are what are the results? Yeah.
I'm glad you asked. Okay. I will pull them all
up right now. So, Gemini's in last again. They
all started with a,000 bucks real money. Gemini
is at $445. Grock is at $1451. So, it's up 45%.
I'm surprised by that. Yeah. In like 5 months.
Perplexity is at $1,731 and Chetch is at $1,739.
Holy crap. 70% each. So, they're up 70% and they
both own currently only they both own SOL, that
semiconductor triple leverage one. And then chat
also owns the TQQQ, the triple leveraged NASDAQ
one. I meant to ask you this question earlier.
What models are Perplexity using? Yeah. Yeah.
Perplexity, it doesn't seem to use Grock very
much. So, it's usually using Claude, Opus, Chat,
and Gemini. And then every now and then it'll like
I'll see like a random Chinese one of
those open source models. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. But it's choosing which model to use. You're
not Yeah. No, it trudges. I I never tell it. So,
yeah. Interesting. Yeah. So, they're both up a
little over 70%. Oh, I just refreshed it. Chat
just went up another few bucks. Okay. Claude,
though, is at 2400 bucks. Yeah. So, 1,000
has gone to 2400. And uh Yeah, Claude's killing
it. So, everybody just needs to try to catch
up to Claude on here. Oh my gosh. Yeah. So, in
total, my 5,000 is like $7,800. Jeez Louise. Yeah.
And that's with so Gemini being horrible%. Yeah.
Okay. Now, what is from the day you started, what
is the market up or down? Oh, good question. Okay.
So, since I started, the S&P has gone from 6800
to 7,100%. Yeah. So, S&P's up five. My AI group
together is up 60 and Claude is more than doubled.
So overall, you've 12xed the market. Yeah. And
you've like 30xed unclog. Yeah. And I've been
keeping my kids in the loop on this because I told
them that this is basically their college fund
to basically or is is Yeah. This will cover one
semester for one of you. Two semesters at BYU.
Yeah. Yeah. You know, cuz I've wanted to teach
them about stocks. Yeah. And and just investing in
general. Um, but it's not always the most exciting
topic, but this is pretty exciting to them
because I'm like, "Hey, look at Claude. Oh, look
at chat. Look at Oh, look what Google messed us
up with, you know, Gemini." So, yeah, they are a
lot more excited to hear the weekly updates. Um,
yeah. Than than I think they otherwise would have
been. Well, for my kids, I would love to have them
do this. I will give them $100. They can split it
up between the five models or whatever. That way
they can learn AI, they can learn prompting,
and they can learn investing allin-one. Yeah.
Yeah. Totally. Yeah. And we'll charge 20%
interest. Yeah. Totally should. It's always
good to charge your kids interest. Make them
learn how the real world works. Clip that. Yeah.
Okay. So, to recap, it's been 6 months. It's not
over yet. Theoretically, you still could lose all
your money. Yeah. But the market's been fairly
flat. At least, you know, in this market, 5% is
is fairly flat. Yeah. But you've outperformed by
10 to 30x. Yeah. And I think that the next six
months, the market is going to go up more than it
has. And I think that these holdings that they're
in currently at least will even do more than what
the market will do over the next 6 months, too.
So, it'll be interesting. I could do like a year
update with you uh to see what happens one year in
or who won because uh yeah, I think it's going
to keep I think they're doing a good job. I think
it's going to keep going up. Yeah, I recorded
another video like this where I did the same test
but with one day expiring options. So, we'll link
to that. Well, Brandon, where can we find you?
Brandon Doyle on on X and something like
that on Instagram and uh yeah, you can uh
look us up on uh tkowners.com too if you want to
join a community with a bunch of entrepreneurs.
Uh good times. Okay, thanks Brandon. Yeah,
thanks. If you like this content, please
share with a friend, hit a like or a comment
below, and we'll see you next time on the Kerner